[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which time zone(s) is Lake Ontario located?", "correct_answer": "Eastern", "incorrect_answers": ["Central", "Central and Mountain", "Eastern and Central"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the price that Jabba settles on with the Bounty Hunter for Chewbacca?", "correct_answer": "35,000 credits", "incorrect_answers": ["40,000 credits", "50,000 credits", "25,000 credits"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who are the wallet thieves in the movie Dirty Dancing?", "correct_answer": "The Shumachers", "incorrect_answers": ["The Housemans", "The Pressmans", "The Sheldricks"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the opening credits of the movie The Breakfast Club, the Man of the Year plaque was shown. Whose picture was on it?", "correct_answer": "Carl the Janitor", "incorrect_answers": ["Andrew Clark", "Mr. Vernon", "John Bender"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How big is a firkin?", "correct_answer": "9 gallons", "incorrect_answers": ["9 pounds", "9 square miles", "9 yards"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the town that Clark Kent calls home in the Superman movies?", "correct_answer": "Smallville", "incorrect_answers": ["New York", "Metropolis", "Boston"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What day is commonly called Black Friday in the United States?", "correct_answer": "The Friday after Thanksgiving", "incorrect_answers": ["The Friday after Easter", "The first Friday of the year", "Friday the 13th"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which sci-fi comedy features a character who renames himself Johnny 5?", "correct_answer": "Short Circuit", "incorrect_answers": ["Escape to Witch Mountain", "RoboCop", "Honey, I Shrunk the Kids"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does Mick Dundee say when he sees the thief holding a knife in the 1986 movie Crocodile Dundee?", "correct_answer": "Thats not a knife.", "incorrect_answers": ["Holly cow, were going to die!", "What the hell is this?", "Good Lord, Im so scared!"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Few animals inhabit the North Pole. Which of these types of animals can never be seen there?", "correct_answer": "Penguins", "incorrect_answers": ["Bears", "Birds", "Fish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where was a depiction of a domino tile included in 2008?", "correct_answer": "In Unicode", "incorrect_answers": ["In the flag of Nicaragua", "In the Chinese alphabet", "In Microsofts logo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed the 2007 animated movie Meet the Robinsons?", "correct_answer": "Stephen J. Anderson", "incorrect_answers": ["Kenny Ortega", "Stanley Jeffers", "Michelle Bochner"]}]